All the panels are frozen, then the bag is activated and the bag is extended to the appropriate position.
Thank you for watching and see you in the next video.
After the length is increased to the appropriate length, freeze the tree.
Activate the top layer to adjust the sleeve part.
It is best to adjust the size of the top layer before the size of the top layer is reduced to 5.
Otherwise, the speed of operation will be slow and it is not convenient to check the effect.
Extend the side of the sleeve to the length of the sleeve.
After extending the sleeve, the panel will penetrate the model's hand.
In order to quickly wear the sleeve out, you can use the selection grid tool.
Select the grid in the 2D window and pull the grid out in the 3D window.
After opening the model, the fabric will no longer be interspersed with the model.
After additional adjustment, continue to extend the sleeve.
After continuing to extend the sleeve, the fabric will no longer be interspersed with the model.
After the length is increased, the panel will be interspersed with the model.
When using the selection grid tool,
When using the tool, press Shift and Ctrl keys at the same time, and drag and drop the mouse to select multiple webpages.
Select all the penetrating webpages and pull them out, then turn on the simulation and put on the costume.
If the hem of the sleeve is not very good, reduce the fineness of the hem and simulate again.
接着我们开始制作披薄。
Create a rectangular board
Make the board wider and longer
Move the board to the center of the board
Add a pin to the board
Then open the simulation and hang the board on the board
Then drag the board to the center of the board
Remove the fixing pin in the back and pull the thinning board to start the simulation.
After a short time, pause the simulation and sew the two boards together.
Then remove the fixing pin on the front side and drag it to adjust the placement of the board.
Select the new fabric for the thinning board.
Make sure the thinning board is on the front side of the thinning board.
Make sure the thinning board is on the front side.
To make the thinning board stack effect, reduce the end speed to 80%.
Dashing over all the the lining, sometimes you may feel that theINDIRA more splendid pattern
and look Enough thinning with thin thinning board.
And gradually make the thinning board thin once again.
While the thinning board sticking to the fabric is still plastic completed,
What are 안녕 squad Antenna Panel designing.
Change the pre-set physical properties of the plated fabric to the formwork material.
After stabilizing, reduce the diameter of the particle and the diameter of the surface.
After adjusting, add a row of fixed needles on both sides.
Increase the slope rate gradually to 100%.
Then simulate.
Adjust the slope rate gradually to 100%.
Then activate the skirt version to modify the wrinkle effect of the skirt.
After activating, you will find that the wrinkle of the skirt version is not detailed enough.
You can reduce the particle diameter first to see the effect.
At present, the grid is a triangular grid.
The top point transition itself will not be smooth, so you can try to reset the grid.
After resetting the grid, the grid will be re-arranged according to the position of the panels in the 2D window.
After resetting the grid, you can clearly see that the wrinkle of the wrinkle is smooth.
These are contrast images.
You can see that the same file has different grid type effects.
Among them,
the one after resetting the grid is the smoothest.
Therefore, we choose to reset the grid.
When modeling, if there is a gap between the model's hand and foot,
it is usually because the model's grid is relatively small and the clothing grid is relatively large.
Therefore, you need to reduce the particle diameter and continue to simulate.
After the simulation is stable and there is no gap, you can move all the panels.
Previously, we applied four-dimensional fabric to the clothing.
This kind of fabric is relatively soft, but it is very light.
When the density of the fabric is lower, the effect of natural water is not obvious enough.
Activate these panels.
Increase the density of the fabric.
When I launch the chamfer.
I can see the material is almost hard.
I press the chamfer.
The material falls off when the fabric falls off.
This kind of simple Nadam's hanfu is already finished.
See you in the next video.
Bye bye!